OVER IN CHICAGO, SAME THING.
MAYOR JOHNSON CREATED NO ICE
ZONES AFTER AGENTS GOT BENGHAZIED.
WHEN IN ANTIFA, BONNIE AND
CLYDE RAMMED AGENTS WITH THEIR
CARS.
THERE WAS A CALL FOR BACKUP, BUT
A STAND-DOWN ORDER WENT OUT ON
THE RADIO.
THEY GOT BOOKED, BUT A DEMOCRAT
BACK JUDGE JUST RELEASED THEM
FOR HAVING GOOD TIES TO THE
COMMUNITY.
THE WOMAN, WHO IS A TEACHER, IS
ACCUSED OF FOLLOWING ICE AGENTS
IN THE CAR FOR 30 MINUTES, DOXING
THEM LIVE ON FACEBOOK, HAD A GUN
IN THE CAR AND RAMMED THEM.
PROSECUTORS SAY THEY'RE EXTREMELY
DANGEROUS.
ICE AGENTS ALREADY HAVE BOUNIES ON
THEIR HEADS AND THESE JUDGES ARE
MAKING IT TOO EASY.
A LATIN KING SHOT CALLER JUST
PUT OUT A $10,000 HIT OUT ON A
BORDER PATROL COMMANDER.
WHOSE SIDE ARE THESE PEOPLE ON?